http://www.gmnameplate.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
All GMN divisions are currently operating and meeting production commitments.
The COVID-19 situation is extremely fluid and the latest developments will be posted here as they become available.
Privacy Policy
We are committed to respecting your online privacy and understand the importance of protecting and appropriately managing any personal information you share with us. This privacy policy is intended to detail the care with which we will treat your personal information.Personal Information as it is used in this privacy policy is defined as any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, physical address and email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. With a few exceptions, you can visit GM Nameplate’s web pages without providing any personal information or identifying yourself in any way.If you choose to provide us with your personal information to access sections of our website which require it, we will not use or transfer your information to any third party and will only use the information you have provided in ways for which you have expressly given GM Nameplate permission. Personal Information will be accessible internally to those employees of GM Nameplate who logically require access to the information in the course of their normal responsibilities.Cookies and tracking technologiesSome of our web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies to gather personal information such as internet domain and host names, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software and operating system types, clickstream patterns, and dates and times that our site is accessed. The information gathered is used to help GM Nameplate improve its website and the content provided, as well as assisting in the development and analysis of trends and statistics.NoticeIn all instances where personal information is collected, GM Nameplate will state how the information will be used and why it is being gathered. GM Nameplate will not release personal information to any third party who is not bound to act on GM Nameplate’s behalf without the express consent of the user.ChoiceYou, as the web user, will always have the choice whether or not to provide personal information to GM Nameplate. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you will still have access to most of GM Nameplate’s website, but you may be unable to access certain options or services.SecurityGM Nameplate will take reasonable care to protect any stored Personal Information from unauthorized access or disclosure.Your ConsentYour use of this web site will serve as your consent to the terms of GM Nameplate’s online privacy policy as stated above. Should GM Nameplate’s online privacy policy change, reasonable measures will be taken to inform all users of such changes.
Consultation
Prototype
Quote
Sample
Close X
